asiamiles.com 2009-06-01

# Asia Miles - About Asia Miles > Privacy Policy

## Commitment to Personal Data Protection

We are committed to protecting your personal data privacy. To ensure that you can make informed decisions and feel confident about providing to us Data (as defined in section 2) relating to you, we outline in this notice our practices and the choices you have concerning the collection and use of your Data.

Moreover, to better protect the Data, certain areas of the website or on our mobile services channels are inaccessible unless you supply individually identifiable and verifiable information, such as your Asia Miles Username / Membership Number and Password / PIN.

Back to Top

We request information in several areas of our website, mobile services and other channels. The types of information we collect ("Data") may include but not limited to:

  1. User name and password
  2. Name
  3. Gender
  4. Date of birth
  5. Mailing address
  6. Email address
  7. Country of residence
  8. ID or Passport number
  9. Nationality
  10. Telephone number
  11. Fax number
  12. Frequent flyer programme number
  13. Company name and job title
  14. Credit card information including name of cardholder, credit card number, credit card billing address and expiry date
  15. Travel details including: 
    1. Flight information - flight number, arrival and departure dates and time, as well as origin and destination
    2. Travel companions' personal information - names, identification card or passport numbers and their frequent flyer programme numbers
    3. Type and number of travel document
    4. Seat and meal preferences
    5. Flight and hotel preferences when using OAG Travel Planner
  16. Business information: business address, total number of employees, industry type, occupation and position/seniority of those who register as a member of Asia Miles.
  17. Contact information of the recipient(s) (where applicable) when sending ecards from the website
  18. Other information such as written and spoken language, leisure and business travel preferences

Certain Data (particularly relating to your personal information and contact information) are required for specific services and if you fail to supply such Data as requested from each specific service, we may be unable to deliver you the services in full.

Back to Top

## Purposes for which the Data are collected and used

We may use the Data you provide for one or more of the following purposes:

  1. To assess and process your application to join Asia Miles;
  2. To process your request for purchasing product(s) and service(s) that may be offered to you;
  3. To process or confirm your travel arrangements;
  4. To fulfil your request when you use our online, mobile or other services;
  5. To contact you regarding your enquiries;
  6. For the operations of Asia Miles including mileage tracking, delivery of associated benefits and services, ongoing research and programme development, as well as delivering news and information to Asia Miles members;
  7. For marketing, promotional and customer management purposes, such as sending you updates on latest offers and promotions in connection with Asia Miles;
  8. For identification and verification purposes;
  9. For reference and record in connection with Asia Miles membership;
  10. For disclosing the winner of a contest conducted by us or on our behalf;
  11. For the use of any of our subsidiaries, associate companies and/or business associates in connection with any of the above purposes and/or services such companies and associates may be offering to you from time to time.

We may from time to time also use aggregate non-identifying information about our customers to better design our website and/or to improve our products and services. This means we may provide this information to third parties. However, this information will not identify any individual user in particular.

Except as provided below, we will never knowingly or intentionally use or share the Data provided to us online in ways unrelated to the purposes aforementioned. Back to Top

## How to Access or Correct Your Data

You are entitled to access and make changes to any Data relating to you held by us.  It is advisable that you should update the Data held by us whenever there is a change and changes to certain Data may be made online at [www.asiamiles.com](http://www.asiamiles.com/). To protect the privacy and security of your Data, your Asia Miles username / membership number and password / PIN are required to gain access or make changes to your personal profile.

If you wish to obtain a copy of any of your Data or if you believe that the Data relating to you which we collect and maintain is inaccurate, you may also write to us at the address below.

A request for access to data or correction of data or for information regarding policies and practices and kinds of data held by us may be sent to us at the following address or via feedback form at [asiamiles.com](http://www.asiamiles.com/am/en/about/contact?format=popup):-

The Data Protection Officer  
Cathay Pacific Loyalty Programmes  
6th Floor Cathay Pacific City,  
8 Scenic Road,  
Hong Kong International Airport, Lantau, Hong Kong.

In accordance with the terms of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region, we have the right to charge a reasonable fee for the processing of any data access request.

Back to Top

A cookie is an alphanumeric string of identifier that websites of the Cathay Pacific group companies (e.g. cathaypacific.com, dragonair.com, asiamiles.com) use to transfer to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk. With the use of cookies, we can better serve you and/or maintain your information across multiple pages within or across one or more sessions. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in future.

Two types of cookies are used on this website:  
**Session Cookies** , which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site.

**Persistent Cookies** , which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you.

**Examples of How we use Cookies on our Site and what Information we collect**

_Session Cookies_

  * To allow you to carry information across pages of our site and avoid having to re-enter information, such as logging in for every page.
  * Within registration to allow you to access stored information.

_Persistent Cookies_

  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our site, and to help us improve the structure of our website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.
  * To store your chosen country homepage destination.
  * To store the username in login box if Asia Miles member checks the "Save No./Username" option.

_Third Party Cookies_

  * To determine and track site traffic coming in from advertisement banners been placed on third parties' websites.

**Disabling / Enabling Cookies**

All browser releases from 4.0 and beyond have a "cookie filter" imbedded in the Privacy settings.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features on our site if cookies acceptance have been disabled completely.

Whilst currently we are only using cookie in the ways we have stated out, new cookies will be implemented as necessary in order to better serve you.

**Log Files**

We may collect information regarding your IP address, browser type, domain name and access time. This information is used for our own research purposes and is separate from the Data. We do not link IP addresses to any personal information. In rare instances, IP addresses may be used to assist in deterring and/or preventing abusive or criminal activity on the website.

Back to Top

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To maintain the accuracy of the Data, as well as preventing unauthorized access to and ensuring the correct use of the Data, we have carried out appropriate physical, electronic and managerial measures to safeguard and secure the Data we collect.

We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol - an industry standard for encryption over the Internet, to protect the Data we collect online. When you type in sensitive information such as credit card details, it will be automatically converted into codes before being securely dispatched over the Internet.

Back to Top

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is our primary concern. Hence, we will not knowingly collect or maintain Data on our website from those who are under 18 years of age except with the consent of such child’s parent or guardian.

Back to Top

Protecting the privacy of children is our primary concern. Hence, we will not knowingly collect or maintain Data on our website from those who are under 18 years of age except with the consent of such child’s parent or guardian.

Back to Top

## Disclosure and Transfer of Data

We may disclose and transfer Data (whether within or outside of Hong Kong) to our subsidiaries, associated companies and/or business associates and other persons who we consider appropriate in connection with the services and products provided or to be provided to you; to facilitate communication of news and information about such services and products; and/or otherwise relating to the purposes mentioned above.

We may also disclose the Data when required by law or court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities, or in the good faith that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including and without limitation to protect our rights or properties or the rights or properties of our subsidiaries or associated companies. This also applies when we have reason to believe that disclosing the Data is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.

Back to Top

## Changes to Privacy Statement

We will post on our website at www.asiamiles.com any changes to our privacy statement so that you are always informed of the way we collect and use the Data. If at any point we wish to use the Data you submitted under this current statement for a different purpose, you will be given the opportunity to opt out or otherwise prevent us from making such use of your Data.

Back to Top

You always have ultimate choice and control of the Data we store, as well as the types of information you would like to receive from us. When you register as a member of Asia Miles or as a general site user, you will have the choice of receiving, or not receiving, promotional materials from us. We will occasionally send you updates about our latest products and services, as well as special offers to those who subscribe to such services.

Should you decide not to receive any updates from us, please specify your choice on the Profile Update pages after logging into the Members Area or you may write to us at the above address in section 4 to unsubscribe to such updates.

**This notice is written in English language and may be translated into other languages. In the event of any inconsistency between the English version and the translated version of this notice, the English version shall prevail.**

We respect and will continue to respect the privacy of our Asia Miles customers.

_Cathay Pacific Loyalty Programmes Limited_

Back to Top

Can't find your airport?

View All
